

ABOUT ME

I am an energetic 23-year-old university student from Estonia studying New Media Design at Jönköping University. After graduation, I wish is to work with front-end development. I have previous work experience with UI & UX design, graphic design, and customer service, these experiences have made me enjoy working in a team. I am always eager to learn something new and love to find ways to add creativity to the workplace and projects.

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud HTML & CSS Javascript & Javascript frameworks PHP & WordPress Figma

Link to my portfolio https://liislepler.github.io/portfolio

LANGUAGES

Estonian - native proficiency
English - full professional proficiency
Swedish - limited proficiency
German - elementary proficiency

CONTACT

liislepler@gmail.com +372 54558338 Jönköping, Sweden

LIIS LEPLER

EDUCATION

PELGULINNA GÜMNAASIUM (Estonia)

Upper-Secondary Education

2016 - 2019 | Graduated in the field of Arts with honors

JÖNKÖPING UNIVERSITY (Sweden)

Degree of Bachelor in Informatics (New Media Design)

2020-2023 | Focus on Web Development and Graphic Design

Taken courses such as Web and User Interface Design, Client-side Programming, Graphic Design for New Media, Client-Server Communication, Interaction Design, Motion Graphics, User Research

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI & UX DESIGN INTERN

World Simplified UG

02/2022 - 06/2022

- Being part of designing a new website platform for a start-up company
- · Designing the company's graphical profile
- Use of Figma

DESIGN FREELANCING

Book design for print (store link) 10/2021 - 11/2021

 Text and pictures alignment for a childrens' book done in Adobe InDesign

SALES ASSISTENT IN AN ELECTRONICS STORE

Nordic Digital AS

01/2020 - 08/2020

 Professional customer service in the field of technology and photography

SALES ASSISTENT IN A CLOTHING STORE

Apranga Group

08/2019 - 11/2019